TEAM J GANG - Justin Mobahir, Jomin Zhang
Activity 2
1) A deck is made up of cards.
2) 6 cards
3)  String[] rank={"A","2","3", "4", "5", "6" , "7" , "8" , "9", "10", "Jack", "Queen", "King"};
    String[] suit={"hearts","spades","diamonds", "clovers"};
	int[] val={11,2,3,4,5,6,7,8,9,10,10,10,10};
4) Yes, since the point values are assigned by "index" and the first element of rank corrseponds with the first element of val. 
   Otherwise the point values would be assigned to the wrong cards.

Activity 3
1) public static String flip() {
    double chances = 0.66;
    if (Math.random() < chances){
        return "heads";
    }
    else {
        return "tails";
    }
}
2) public static boolean arePermutations(int[] arr1, int[] arr2){
    for (int i = 0; i < arr1.length; i++){
       for (int j = 0; j < arr2.length; j++){
           if (arr1[i] == arr2[j]){
              break;
           }
           if (j == arr2.length - 1){
             return false;
           }
       }
    }
    return true;
}
3)0, 1

Activity 6
1) 5S + 6C or 5C + 6C
2) Yes, because cards can only be removed in pairs that add up to 11 or in JQK, and so if 3 cards are left they must be the JQK.
3) No, because the only thing that matters is the rank and each rank only pairs up with another rank (or in the case of the JQK they go together) 
   and therefore it doesn't matter what order they are removed in. If two pairs are on the board, removing one or the other does not give more or less options.

Activity 7
1) A deck of cards.
   Card[] Deck + Cards
2)  Create a board
    Create a deck
    Shuffle the deck
    Deal cards
    Look for legal moves
    If none game is over, if deck is empty game is won, otherwise it is a loss
3) Yes
4a) In the constructor and the newGame()
4b) In the isLegal() and anotherPlayIsPossible()
4c) 0:0, 1:1, 2:3, 3:6, 4:7
4d) 
String retVal = "";
    for (int i = 0; i < cIndexes.length(); i++) {
       retVal += cIndexes.get(i) + ", ";
    }
    return retVal;
4e) anotherPlayIsPossible()

Activity 8
1) All of them use a deck of cards which are made up of the same type of cards. They all use a board. 
   They have different board sizes and rules.
2) ElevensBoard inherits from board and uses the board constructor with its own values.
3) Yes

Activity 9
1) The functionality of size is the same across all the boards which is to return the size. The actual size of the board is determined by its constructor
2) The selection and replacement of cards function the same across all the games
3) Using an interface would still allow for isLegal() and anotherPlayIsPossible() to be called polymorphically.